<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="https://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="https://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Fun &amp; Frolic Mirth Peddlers</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Yay!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 01:44:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Jeeves &#038; Wooster Monster Hunters</title>
		<link>/2019/10/jeeves-wooster-monster-hunters/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 01:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The idea for&#160;Jeeves &#38; Wooster Monster Hunters came to me in a dream one night. As there was no system I felt I could run this in, I have created a game systems inspired by some of the simple coin flip mechanics of the game Clink. This game is currently under development and being play [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The idea for&nbsp;<em>Jeeves &amp; Wooster Monster Hunters</em> came to me in a dream one night. As there was no system I felt I could run this in, I have created a game systems inspired by some of the simple coin flip mechanics of the game <em><a href="https://www.drivethrurpg.com/product/236659/Clink-RPG">Clink</a></em>. </p>



<p>This game is currently under development and being play tested. If you are interested in helping play test it you can contact me at <a href="mailto:info@mirthpeddlers.com">info@mirthpeddlers.com</a></p>



<p>If you don&#8217;t know <em><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeeves_and_Wooster">Jeeves and Wooster</a></em> then there is no time like the present to get acquainted! You can read P.G. Wodehouse&#8217;s original book <a href="https://www.gutenberg.org/ebooks/59254">The Inimitable Jeeves</a> via Project Gutenberg. Or watch the hilarious BBC TV version starring Stephen Fry and Hugh Laurie via YouTube!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-4-3 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe loading="lazy" title="Full Episode Jeeves and Wooster S01 E1   In court after the boat race" width="500" height="375" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tk7pk58Bq4Q?feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2>J&amp;W:MH Scenario: The Spring Festival</h2>



<p>The small countryside town of Market Snodsbury has celebrated the Spring Equinox for as long as anyone can remember. Bertie Wooster couldn&#8217;t care less about the festival but Aunt Dahlia has insisted he come out to the countryside. She’s quite certain that she will win the coveted trophy for the flower arrangement competition but needs Wooster’s help. You see her prize rose garden has been acting very peculiar as of late. Oh, there is also the trouble with Wooster’s pal Bingo who seems to have gotten himself head over heels in love again — this time with the judge of the flower competition! </p>



<p>Will Bingo finally find his true love? Who will win the Market Snodsbury Spring Festival flower competition? And why are all the servants terrified of the Brinkley Court rose garden? How will Wooster get himself out of this thorny trouble? Well I’m sure Jeeves has a few tricks up his sleeve to help out. Find out what happens in the next episode of&nbsp;<em>Jeeves &amp; Wooster: Monster Hunters!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ghost Census</title>
		<link>/2019/10/ghost-census/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I created Ghost Census as a business card sized game to be passed out at Big Bad Con 2019. It was a hit little game and so I revised it as a print-in-play party game! You remember your Ghost Census training right? …Of course you do! Well then this should be no problem for you! [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I created Ghost Census as a business card sized game to be passed out at <a href="https://bigbadcon.com/">Big Bad Con</a> 2019. It was a hit little game and so I revised it as a print-in-play party game! </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>You remember your Ghost Census training right? …Of course you do! Well then this should be no problem for you! Just&nbsp;work&nbsp;with your fellow ghost census workers to&nbsp;interview the ghosts in your area so they can all be counted!</p></blockquote>



<p>Ghost Census is design to be played with 6 or more people — the more the better! It works as a great casual ice-breaker game. It can be played right at the beginning or played throughout the event casually with the a revel of the various ghosts interviewed at the end. Works great for a Halloween <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f383.png" alt="🎃" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f47b.png" alt="👻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Party!</p>



<h2>Downloads</h2>



<p>Ghost Census is available as a pay what you want downloadable print-n-play PDF. Comes with 6-up on letter sized paper, business card sized design if you want to get your own printed professionally, and a how to play instruction sheet.</p>



<figure><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://itch.io/embed/499974?linkback=true" width="552" height="167"></iframe></figure>



<h2>One of the ghosts at Big Bad Con 2019!</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="1024" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/4e0ISr-1024x1024.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-329" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/4e0ISr-1024x1024.jpeg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/10/4e0ISr-150x150.jpeg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/10/4e0ISr-300x300.jpeg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/10/4e0ISr-768x768.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
