<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="https://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="https://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>RPG &#8211; Fun &amp; Frolic Mirth Peddlers</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/rpg/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Yay!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 01:56:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>At the Corner of Mean and Meow</title>
		<link>/2018/10/at-the-corner-of-mean-and-meow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 22:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[RPG]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A walking roleplaying nano-game about feral cats trying to survive on the mean streets of the city. Downloads At the Corner of Mean and Meow is available as a pay what you want downloadable PDF]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A walking roleplaying nano-game about feral cats trying to survive on the mean streets of the city.</p>



<h2>Downloads</h2>



<p>At the Corner of Mean and Meow is available as a pay what you want downloadable PDF</p>



<figure><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://itch.io/embed/420878?linkback=true" width="552" height="167"></iframe></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img loading="lazy" width="791" height="1024" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/At-the-Corner-of-Mean-and-Meow-1-791x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-299" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/At-the-Corner-of-Mean-and-Meow-1-791x1024.png 791w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/10/At-the-Corner-of-Mean-and-Meow-1-232x300.png 232w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/10/At-the-Corner-of-Mean-and-Meow-1-768x994.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 791px) 100vw, 791px" /></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fist of Liberty</title>
		<link>/2018/01/fist-of-liberty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[RPG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tabletop Game]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=273</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[UPDATE Oct 15, 2019: This game is on hold indefinitely. While I had some fun play test sessions, I realized the reason the games were fun more had to do with my ability to run a good session and not because the rules supported fun play. There is still some good in there which I [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>UPDATE Oct 15, 2019:</strong> This game is on hold indefinitely. While I had some fun play test sessions, I realized the reason the games were fun more had to do with my ability to run a good session and not because the rules supported fun play. There is still some good in there which I may repurpose or release in some form at some point.</p>
<hr>
<p>Introducing a new game I&#8217;m working on called Fist of Liberty!</p>
<p>Fist of Liberty is a tabletop roleplaying game about normal people attempting to overthrow the oppressive state. Inspired by such dystopian classics such as 1984 and Brave New World, and films like eTHX-1138, Brazil, Max Headroom, Idiocracy, Equilibrium, and The Hunger Games. It is a one shot game designed to be played in 4-6 hours. Every game of Fist of Liberty is different as it starts with a fast cooperative world building and character building session!</p>
<p>The game mechanics for Fist of Liberty are inspired by the excellent game <a href="https://payhip.com/b/Ux9O">Soth</a> by <a href="https://stevehickeygames.blogspot.co.nz/">Steve Hickey</a> and also by&nbsp;<a href="https://apocalypse-world.com/">Apocalypse World</a>. If you haven&#8217;t played either I highly recommend both!</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve already started play testing the game. Several of the play tests happened at <a href="https://www.bigbadcon.com/">Big Bad Con</a> 2017 which were a whole lot of fun and very instrumental in helping me improve the game and develop it further. I will be running additional play test sessions sometime soon so if you are interested in joining please drop me a line at info@mirthpeddlers.com</p>
<p>You can also sign up to our mailing list to keep abreast of developments</p>
<p><!-- Begin MailChimp Signup Form --></p>
<style type="text/css">
	#mc_embed_signup{background:#fff; clear:left; font:14px Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; }<br />
	/* Add your own MailChimp form style overrides in your site stylesheet or in this style block.<br />
	   We recommend moving this block and the preceding CSS link to the HEAD of your HTML file. */<br />
</style>
<div id="mc_embed_signup">
<form id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" action="https://balsaman.us2.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=04d84b9e1399b42e80fde93ba&amp;id=6bb5cc3a67" method="post" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" novalidate="" target="_blank">
<div id="mc_embed_signup_scroll">
<h2>Subscribe to our mailing list</h2>
<div class="indicates-required"><span class="asterisk">*</span> indicates required</div>
<div class="mc-field-group"><label for="mce-EMAIL">Email Address <span class="asterisk">*</span><br />
</label><br />
<input id="mce-EMAIL" class="required email" name="EMAIL" type="email" value=""></div>
<div class="mc-field-group"><label for="mce-FNAME">First Name </label><br />
<input id="mce-FNAME" class="" name="FNAME" type="text" value=""></div>
<div class="mc-field-group"><label for="mce-LNAME">Last Name </label><br />
<input id="mce-LNAME" class="" name="LNAME" type="text" value=""></div>
<div id="mce-responses" class="clear">
<div id="mce-error-response" class="response" style="display: none;"></div>
<div id="mce-success-response" class="response" style="display: none;"></div>
</div>
<p><!-- real people should not fill this in and expect good things - do not remove this or risk form bot signups--></p>
<div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;" aria-hidden="true"><input tabindex="-1" name="b_04d84b9e1399b42e80fde93ba_6bb5cc3a67" type="text" value=""></div>
<div class="clear"><input id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button" name="subscribe" type="submit" value="Subscribe"></div>
</div>
</form>
</div>
<p><script type="text/javascript" src="//s3.amazonaws.com/downloads.mailchimp.com/js/mc-validate.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">(function($) {window.fnames = new Array(); window.ftypes = new Array();fnames[0]='EMAIL';ftypes[0]='email';fnames[1]='FNAME';ftypes[1]='text';fnames[2]='LNAME';ftypes[2]='text';}(jQuery));var $mcj = jQuery.noConflict(true);</script><br />
<!--End mc_embed_signup--></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apocalypse Warren</title>
		<link>/2016/12/apocalypse-warren/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 08:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[RPG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tabletop Game]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=217</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I present Apocalypse Warren, a world playset that brings the apocalypse back into The Warren! A time of chaos… ruined dreams… this wasted land… For reasons long forgotten, two mighty human warrior tribes went to war and touched off a blaze which engulfed them all. Their world crumbled. Now in this wasted world, life does as it [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I present Apocalypse Warren, a world playset that brings the apocalypse back into <a href="https://bullypulpitgames.com/games/the-warren/">The Warren</a>!</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><strong>A time of chaos… ruined dreams… this wasted land…</strong> For reasons long forgotten, two mighty human warrior tribes went to war and touched off a blaze which engulfed them all. Their world crumbled. Now in this wasted world, life does as it always — it struggles to hang on. The rains come rarely anymore but rabbits learned to survive the harsh reality of the desert, long before humans ruined the world. As a desert rabbit, you’ve learned to forage for scarce food mainly during dawn and dusk when the sun is muted, always keeping an ear out for hungry snakes, monitor lizards, kites, and dingos. The human survivors are an unpredictable danger as they still cling to their machines and their war, strewing chaos across the land. You once could have asked the ancestors for help — a trick rabbits learned from the bilby — but with the cataclysm came a strange terrifying Wind howling outside this world which tore apart the Dreaming.</p></blockquote>



<p>I created this Warren World playset while home sick in bed watching Watership Down and all the Mad Max movies. After many revisions, I then ran it at <a href="https://www.bigbadcon.com/">Big Bad Con</a> 2016 for some wonderfully brave rabbits. It&#8217;s now ready for any and all rabbits who want to try and find a way to survive in this post-apocalyptic wasted land!</p>



<h2>Downloads</h2>



<p>Apocalypse Warren is available for download as a pay what you want PDF. The game includes a playset with NPCs, Predators, and Threats; info on the Human Settlement, the Bilby, the Strange and Horrible Wind that Howls Outside This World, a custom move &#8220;Perk Up Your Ears and Listen to the Wind, and a map of the surrounding area.</p>



<figure><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://itch.io/embed/420852?linkback=true" width="552" height="167"></iframe></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B_x5XNahtqzveDV0cXdmX0tPRDg/view?usp=sharing"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="791" src="/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p1-1024x791.png" alt="warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p1" class="wp-image-222" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p1-1024x791.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p1-300x232.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p1-768x593.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p1.png 1584w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="791" src="/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p4-1024x791.jpg" alt="warren world apocalypse warren map" class="wp-image-225" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p4-1024x791.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p4-300x232.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p4-768x593.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/12/warren_world-apocalypse_warren-p4.jpg 1584w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Raver and the Bear</title>
		<link>/2015/05/the-raver-and-the-bear/</link>
					<comments>/2015/05/the-raver-and-the-bear/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[RPG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tabletop Game]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=163</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I was inspired and made a micro rpg game for David Schirbun’s awesome #200WordRPG challenge called THE RAVER AND THE BEAR! You should check out the 200 Word RPG Challenge site as there are some amazing entries. I especially love LoveInt and Holding On and KillByNumbers but I&#8217;ve honestly barely scratched the surface of all the entries. UPDATE!!! NEW [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I was inspired and made a micro rpg game for David Schirbun’s awesome <a href="https://schirduans.com/david/2015/04/200-word-rpg-challenge.html">#200WordRPG challenge</a> called THE RAVER AND THE BEAR! You should check out the 200 Word RPG Challenge site as there are some amazing entries. I especially love LoveInt and Holding On and KillByNumbers but I&#8217;ve honestly barely scratched the surface of all the entries.</p>



<p><strong>UPDATE!!! NEW RAVER AND THE BEAR – ECLECTIC HIPSTER EXPANSION</strong> with rules for advanced play with the dangerous finicky hipster bear.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img loading="lazy" width="791" height="1024" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/rave-reviews-791x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-204" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/rave-reviews-791x1024.png 791w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/05/rave-reviews-232x300.png 232w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/05/rave-reviews.png 918w" sizes="(max-width: 791px) 100vw, 791px" /></figure>



<h2>Downloads</h2>



<p>THE RAVER AND THE BEAR is available for download as a print-n-play PDF as a pay what you want game!</p>



<figure><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://itch.io/embed/420868?linkback=true" width="552" height="167"></iframe></figure>



<h2>Actual Play Video</h2>



<p>Actual play video from <a href="https://bigbadcon.com/">Big Bad Con</a> 2015!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe loading="lazy" title="The Raver and the Bear game play" width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0RiZsAZM_bA?feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2>HE RAVER AND THE BEAR FAQ</h2>



<ul><li>Once the DJ starts playing, does the bear&#8217;s first check start from anywhere in particular or wherever the bear decides?&nbsp;<em><br>The Bear&#8217;s first check starts as soon as the second album is put on.</em></li><li>I&#8217;m still confused about what order is correct vs reverse vs out of order can you explain it better? <em>Think of the albums as positions on a clock but unlike an analogue clock this clock only has 5 positions on it (1-5) and once it reaches the last position it goes to the first position. The Bear places one album on each position. Let&#8217;s say there are 5 records A,B,C,D,E and the Bear preferred play order is clockwise in this order C&gt;E&gt;B&gt;A&gt;D (since this is a clock it continues and D&gt;C… etc.). Now if the DJ plays C and then E it is in the right clockwise order and the Bear is happy, If the DJ plays C then D then it is in the wrong anti-clockwise reverse order and the Bear is angry and mauls them. If the DJ plays C and then either B or A then the Bear is annoyed as is out of order and the Bear growls</em></li><li>After the DJ gets mauled the first time, should the bear start from the original start place?&nbsp;<em>When the DJ get&#8217;s mauled they just put on another record — either one they played before or a new one. There is no &#8220;start place&#8221; for the Bear&#8217;s music order preferences as it&#8217;s a continuous circle. Let&#8217;s say the Bear&#8217;s preferences are B, A, C, E, D — then the DJ can &#8220;win&#8221; by playing in a row consecutively B, A, C, E, D or A, C, E, D, B or C, E, D, B, A or E, D, B, A, C or D, B, A, C, E.&nbsp;Probably better way of thinking about it is the DJ&nbsp;needs to make the bear happy 4 times in a row&nbsp;by playing albums in&nbsp;the right order.</em></li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2015/05/the-raver-and-the-bear/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unstoppable Power!</title>
		<link>/2015/03/unstoppable-power-playtesting-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Colin Fahrion]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 16:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[RPG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tabletop Game]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[UPDATE Oct 15, 2019: Development for this game is back underway after a long hiatus! I was inspired by the game Bluebeard&#8217;s Bride to completely revise the game centered around the life of a single Hero, with all the players acting as aspects of the Hero&#8217;s humanity. I ran this game at Big Bad Con [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>UPDATE Oct 15, 2019:</strong> Development for this game is back underway after a long hiatus! I was inspired by the game Bluebeard&#8217;s Bride to completely revise the game centered around the life of a single Hero, with all the players acting as aspects of the Hero&#8217;s humanity. I ran this game at Big Bad Con 2019 and it went great. I will be doing more playtesting in the coming months. If you are interested in playtesting contact me at <a href="mailto:info@mirthpeddlers.com">info@mirthpeddlers.com</a></p>
<hr />
<p><strong>UPDATE Jan 28, 2017:</strong> The development for this game is on hiatus. I ran a number of play test sessions and while they were fun overall the game wasn&#8217;t quite working. I have some vague ideas for how to redesign the game but it is on hold.</p>
<hr />
<p>I had a inspiration the other day that superhero games are boring as they only tell the day to day banal tales of laser beam shooting out of peoples eyes. Wouldn’t it be great to tell the full story of what having real power is like? What it’s like to be heroes like Dr Manhattan with powers so beyond mere mortals that it’s hard to relate to anyone or anything?</p>
<div class="text_exposed_show">
<p>The game Unstoppable Power is a one-shot storygame that tells the story of normal people who gain superpowers. And how this ‘gift’ of true power transforms them until they can no longer can relate to the world or people they once knew, and likely leaving irrevocable harm in their wake.</p>
<p>The game mechanics are pretty honed in — simple and designed to help support the story of people facing their own Unstoppable Power. I’ve run a solo play of the game to test the system and it worked great. Next step is running real playtests which is happening soon. If you are interested in play testing Unstoppable Power you can contact me at <a href="mailto:info@mirthpeddlers.com">info@mirthpeddlers.com</a></p>
<p><span data-reactid=".42.1:3:1:$comment452326328258304_452472604910343:0.0.$right.0.$left.0.0.1.$comment-body.0.0">Here’s a quick overview summary of the story that the game told in my solo playtest…<br data-reactid=".42.1:3:1:$comment452326328258304_452472604910343:0.0.$right.0.$left.0.0.1.$comment-body.0.0.$end:0:$3:0" /></span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-reactid=".42.1:3:1:$comment452326328258304_452472604910343:0.0.$right.0.$left.0.0.1.$comment-body.0.3">The story started as Sonny, a retired hit man fighting to save his kidnapped boyfriend. He died in a massive gun battle yet then rose from death as a silent shadow enshrouded assassin — first taking revenge, then fighting crime mostly because he was bored. Time passed and he drifted away from all he once was transforming into a being known only as Operation Shadow by the US government. Project Shadow worked with the Pentagon and CIA to target ISIS — an operation that succeeded in destroying ISIS yet caused massive collateral damage and worldwide outrage. Shunned by a coalition of world governments, the world spanning essence of shadow known as Project Shadow to some and the Dark Djinn to others has the power to destroy entire nations. In fact it accidentally wiped Syria off the map — it was only trying to help! Feared and truly disconnected from the people of the world, it decides for esoteric reasons all it’s own to leave Earth. During a lunar eclipse, it steps to the moon and breaks off a piece the size of the Mount McKinley, then gets on and aims it at the black hole at the center of the Galaxy. A small shadowy part of it however stayed behind on Earth to possess — no possess isn&#8217;t the right word  — to become one with the old boyfriend (his boyfriend?) who was all but left behind so many years ago.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-reactid=".42.1:3:1:$comment452326328258304_452472604910343:0.0.$right.0.$left.0.0.1.$comment-body.0.3">There was a lot more detail I left out, but yeah that’s the kind of wow story you can tell with Unstoppable Power in only a single one-shot game!</span></p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/Unstoppable-Power-v2.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-154" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/Unstoppable-Power-v2.png" alt="Unstoppable-Power-v2" width="693" height="886" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/Unstoppable-Power-v2.png 693w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/03/Unstoppable-Power-v2-235x300.png 235w" sizes="(max-width: 693px) 100vw, 693px" /></a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
